Heh. We never got to the bedroom.
(Sheldon:)Because?
[SCOFFS]
(Penny:)Okay. All right. You know what?
I'll tell you what happened.
Ah. We were young.
(Penny:)We were very much in love,
but we could only communicate...
(Penny:)...through a time-traveling mailbox
at my lake house.
(Sheldon:)It's not enough that you made me watch
that movie, but now you mock me with it?
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, I have a question
about dating and relationships.
(Raj:)You told me
you were gonna have the talk with him.
(Howard:)I've been waiting for someone
to have the talk with me.
(Sheldon:)More to the point, it's about finding a way
to keep Leonard and Stephanie together.
- Oh, I don't think you can.
- Why not?
(Howard:)Look at Leonard's record.
Twenty-seven days with Joyce Kim.